God Almighty uses Prophet T.B. Joshua as a channel of light
to dispel every shade of darkness in the lives of the people
As he leads the congregation in mass prayer, he reveals the root cause
of the problems in the lives of the people through words of prophecy.
There is a woman. You just left your marriage and your husband is begging you to come back
but you are in-between decision.
You are in-between decision.
You left your marriage and your husband is begging you to come back.
You are in-between decision - whether to go or not. Please come.
Jesus loves you. Come.
Sir, I am the one you called who left her husband.
I left my husband and I am trying to decide. Right now, I have not decided to go back.
He was the one who told me to come to church.
You say you are contemplating going back to your husband
because each time you see yourself in the mirror, you are happy.
You have to go back. Okay?
What you have done to your husband is more than what your husband has done to you.
Okay?
So, I will talk to you.
You can't trade anything with that, okay?
Yes, sir.
You know in your home, they don't have settled homes.
Okay. You don't have settled homes.
It is true, sir.
For you to have...
The beginning of your life was disappointment.
Yes, sir. It is true, sir.
You know you started your life with disappointment.
Your first attempt failed before you met this man.
Yes, sir. It is true, sir.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Gloria Albert Egbelo.
The man standing beside me is my husband Albert Egbelo.
Last week Sunday, I sat at the back when the man of God was prophecying.
He said that there was a lady down there who just left her husband.
The husband had been begging her to come back.
She was still contemplating whether to come back or not.
That was when I now came out.
Can you tell us your life experiences in your marriage
that brought about that decision you took to pack out of the house.
Before I left my husband's house, my husband was busy drinking, womanising.
He was not even paying attention to the house because of the women that he kept.
He had other women outside so he wasn't paying attention at all.
Sometimes, he would go and drink and come back very drunk,
be vomiting everwhere so I was tired.
At a point, the parents said that the fault was from me.
So that was why I left the house. I packed my things, carried my baby and left
when my husband starting displaying such behaviours.
I now lost affection - sometimes, I used to tell him, "I hate you!"
I don't know affection at all.
He doesn't even sleep with me.
Anytime he comes close to me, it irritates me.
Even when he uses a spoon to eat, I wash the spoon before I eat with the spoon.
Now tell us what happened when you finally came to The SCOAN.
On one Sunday, I came to the church.
The man of God was then prophecying that there was a lady in the church
that just left her husband and she was in-between deciding whether to come back or not.
That prophecy was very very true.
Because even when I came to the church, I was even saying,
"When I go back, I will not go back to him again".
So before the man of God prophecied and said that there was a lady in the church
that left her husband and she was still contemplating on whether to go back or not.
It is true because I was contemplating, I was so tired. I said, "I'm not going back!"
I said to myself, "Should I go back to this man and continue with this suffering?
No! I will not go back!"
Now, after the prophecy, tell us what happened that brought about the testimony today.
After the prophecy, the man of God prayed for me.
He then invited my husband and prayed for us.
After the prayers, everything just disappeared.
Even my husband has changed. He has turned into a lovely man.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ! Put your hands together beautifully
for the miracle-working God!
Now, people really want to understand the difference.
You said, before now, it got to a stage where the hatred was so terrible
to the extent that after your husband finished using a spoon to eat,
you had to wash the spoon - sterilise it very well before you used it
to really explain the extent of that hatred, that the affection was no longer there.
Tell us the changes you are seeing right now
to confirm that the Lord has delivered you and your husband.
Since after the deliverance, in fact, if my husband is not by my side for a second,
I would start calling him, "Where are you? Come back now!"
My husband doesn't drink; he doesn't do all those things.
He comes back early. Even when a woman is passing, he wouldn't react.
Everything has now changed. Even my behaviour towards him has changed.
I love him so much.
Okay. Before now, each time he was moving with you, he would be looking somewhere else?
Before now, I didn't even move with him because any time he said, "Let's go out,
I would say, "You go! I will come and meet you" because I didn't even want people seeing us around.
But right now, after the deliverance?
Now, he is my...
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
To God be the glory! Only Jesus can do this.
We thank God Almighty. You can imagine a wonderful marriage that is at the verge of divorce.
At the end of the day, the Lord delivered them
and right now, they are reconciled back to the glory of God.
Let's put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Now, before we listen to words of advice from you, let's quickly hear from your husband.
My name is Albert Egbelo.
I'm a deputy superintendent of police. I am a unit commander.
The woman next to me is my dear wife.
What she said rightly - all was right.
I was busy drinking and womanising before.
Lsst week Sunday, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied about her and she was picked out.
After the deliverance and prayers from Prophet T.B. Joshua for my wife and myself,
all the things I used to do - the drinking, following women,
coming back home late - stopped because he prayed for me.
I bless God and thank God for my life and my family.
Okay. Let us now know about the difference between you and your wife.
She said that before now, she didn't want to see you at all.
What are the changes you have seen as a man?
She is wonderful now.
My attention, my mind, everything, the drinking, everything she did not want
has stopped after the deliverance.
Right now, I see her as my angel and everything to me.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
And the area of womanising - what can you say about it?
Well, for those who do not know, there is nothing to gain there because I've been there.
The area of womanising - God has touched me
and there is not any other woman that is far better than my wife.
Thank you.
Amen. Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
We thank God Almight for what He has done in your life and also in the life of your wife.
As a man - many men are listening to you; they want to hear a word of advice from you.
What's your advice to men and to everyone?
My advice - I'm a man.
My advice to all men over the world, particularly the ones seated here is:
They should pay attention to their wifes at home,
pay attention to God, be particularly always prayerful. Thank you.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
Finally, let us also hear a piece of advice from your wife.
Can you advise women and everyone.
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My advice to all women is: When you have a problem or challenges,
although your challenge is telling you to run to God and not go out,
because of those challenges I had to run away
but the challenges were then telling me, "Please, when you are having challenges,
any time you are having challenges with your husband, know that it is not him
but the spirit is disturbing him. Please, run to God, pray for him.
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
God is with us!
Put your hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Yes, that is indeed a wonderful advice.
She said it loud and clear that if she did not run to God,
today, the story would have changed.
We thank God Almighty that the Lord Almighty who she ran to has restored her marriage happily.
We thank God Almighty for her life.
We really rejoice with you greatly.
We also want to advise you to make the Word of God the standard for your life.
As you go and make the Word of God the standard for your life,
always have it at the back of your mind that better is not good enough,
the best is always yet to come.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Mrs Gloria Albert Egbelo & Husband
Prophecy Testimony
TT: Mel Flowers 21/07/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 01/09/2018